illinoisloyalty.com 2019-03-04

# Privacy Policy and Cookie Policy

Last updated: May 24, 2018 

This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use and disclosure of Personal Information when you use our Service. 

We will not use or share your information with anyone except as described in this Privacy Policy and Cookie Policy. 

**We use your Personal Information for providing and improving the Service. By using the Service, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy.** Unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy and Cookie Policy, terms used in this Privacy Policy and Cookie Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms and Conditions, accessible at http://www.illinoisloyalty.com/ 

**Information Collection And Use**

While using our Service, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you. Personally identifiable information may include, but is not limited to, your email address ("Personal Information"). 

We collect this information for the purpose of providing the Service, identifying and communicating with you, responding to your requests/inquiries, servicing your purchase orders, and improving our services. 

**Log Data**

We collect information that your browser sends whenever you visit our Service ("Log Data"). This Log Data may include information such as your computer's Internet Protocol ("IP") address, browser type, browser version, the pages of our Service that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages and other statistics. 

In addition, we may use third party services such as Google Analytics that collect, monitor and analyze this type of information in order to increase our Service's functionality. These third party service providers have their own privacy policies addressing how they use such information. 

**Cookies**

Cookies are files with a small amount of data, which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a web site and transferred to your device. We use cookies to collect information in order to improve our services for you. 

You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. The Help feature on most browsers provide information on how to accept cookies, disable cookies or to notify you when receiving a new cookie. 

If you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some features of our Service and we recommend that you leave them turned on. 

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our Service. Google's use of the DoubleClick cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our Service or other web sites on the Internet. 

You may opt out of the use of the DoubleClick Cookie for interest-based advertising by visiting the [Google Ads Settings](http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/ "Google Ads Settings") web page. 

If you continue to use this site, you are consenting to our use of cookies. 

**What are cookies?**

Cookies are small text files stored on your computer by your web browser at the request of a site you're viewing. This allows the site you're viewing to remember things about you, such as your preferences and history or to keep you logged in. 

Cookies may be stored on your computer for a short time (such as only while your browser is open) or for an extended period of time, even years. Cookies not set by this site will not be accessible to us. 

**Our cookie usage**

This site uses cookies for numerous things, including: 

  * Registration and maintaining your preferences. This includes ensuring that you can stay logged in and keeping the site in the language or appearance that you requested.
  * Analytics. This allows us to determine how people are using the site and improve it.
  * Advertising cookies (possibly third-party). If this site displays advertising, cookies may be set by the advertisers to determine who has viewed an ad or similar things. These cookies may be set by third parties, in which case this site has no ability to read or write these cookies.
  * Other third-party cookies for things like social media sharing. These cookies will generally be set by the third-party independently, so this site will have no ability to access them.

**Additional cookies and those set by third parties**

Additional cookies may be set during the use of the site to remember information as certain actions are being performed, or remembering certain preferences. 

Other cookies may be set by third party service providers which may provide information such as tracking anonymously which users are visiting the site, or set by content embedded into some pages, such as YouTube or other media service providers. 

**Removing/disabling cookies**

Managing your cookies and cookie preferences must be done from within your browser's options/preferences. Here is a list of guides on how to do this for popular browser software: 

**More information about cookies**

To learn more about cookies, and find more information about blocking certain types of cookies, please visit the [ICO website Cookies page](https://ico.org.uk/for-the-public/online/cookies/). 

**Do Not Track Disclosure**

We do not support Do Not Track ("DNT"). Do Not Track is a preference you can set in your web browser to inform websites that you do not want to be tracked. You can enable or disable Do Not Track by visiting the Preferences or Settings page of your web browser. 

**Service Providers**

We may employ third party companies and individuals to facilitate our Service, to provide the Service on our behalf, to perform Service-related services and/or to assist us in analyzing how our Service is used. 

These third parties have access to your Personal Information only to perform specific tasks on our behalf and are obligated not to disclose or use your information for any other purpose. 

**Communications**

We may use your Personal Information to contact you with newsletters, marketing or promotional materials and other information that may be of interest to you. You may opt out of receiving any, or all, of these communications from us by following the unsubscribe link or instructions provided in any email we send or by contacting us. 

**Compliance With Laws**

We will disclose your Personal Information where required to do so by law or subpoena or if we believe that such action is necessary to comply with the law and the reasonable requests of law enforcement or to protect the security or integrity of our Service. 

**Business Transaction**

Fourth Ridge Media Productions, LLC ("us", "we", or "our") operates the http://www.illinoisloyalty.com/ website (the "Service"). 

If Fourth Ridge Media Productions, LLC is involved in a merger, acquisition or asset sale, your Personal Information may be transferred as a business asset. In such cases, we will provide notice before your Personal Information is transferred and/or becomes subject to a different Privacy Policy. 

**Security**

The security of your Personal Information is important to us, and we strive to implement and maintain reasonable, commercially acceptable security procedures and practices appropriate to the nature of the information we store, in order to protect it from unauthorized access, destruction, use, modification, or disclosure. 

However, please be aware that no method of transmission over the internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure and we are unable to guarantee the absolute security of the Personal Information we have collected from you. 

**International Transfer**

Your information, including Personal Information, may be transferred to -- and maintained on -- computers located outside of your state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction where the data protection laws may differ than those from your jurisdiction. 

If you are located outside United States and choose to provide information to us, please note that we transfer the information, including Personal Information, to United States and process it there. 

Your consent to this Privacy Policy and Cookie Policy followed by your submission of such information represents your agreement to that transfer. 

**Links To Other Sites**

Our Service may contain links to other sites that are not operated by us. If you click on a third party link, you will be directed to that third party's site. We strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of every site you visit. 

We have no control over, and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practices of any third party sites or services. 

**Children's Privacy**

Children under the age of 13 ("Children") are not permitted to use our sites and services. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13. If we learn that we have collected personal information from a child under 13, we will take steps to promptly delete such information. If you are a parent or guardian and you learn that your Children have provided us with Personal Information, please contact us. If we discover that a Child under 13 has provided us with Personal Information, we will delete such information from our servers. 

**Changes To This Privacy Policy and Cookie Policy**

This Privacy Policy and Cookie Policy is effective as of May 24, 2018 and will remain in effect except with respect to any changes in its provisions in the future, which will be in effect immediately after being posted on this page. 

We reserve the right to update or change our Privacy Policy and Cookie Policy at any time and you should check this Privacy Policy and Cookie Policy periodically. Your continued use of the Service after we post any modifications to the Privacy Policy and Cookie Policy on this page will constitute your acknowledgment of the modifications and your consent to abide and be bound by the modified Privacy Policy and Cookie Policy. 

**Contact Us**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy and Cookie Policy, please contact us.
